{
  "uniqueId": 37,
  "name": "English Vocabulary Quiz",
  "article": "an",
  "instructions": "Guess the word!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "TEXT_WITH_HINT",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "WEBSTER_ANSWER",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "WITH_HINT",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "BETTER_ENGLISH_DEFINITIONS",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "ANSWER_ONLY",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "in a corresponding manner",
      "answer": "correspondingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ordinal number of fifty in counting order  ",
      "answer": "fiftieth"
    },
    {
      "question": "be on top of",
      "answer": "surmount"
    },
    {
      "question": "the practical application of science to commerce or industry  ",
      "answer": "technology"
    },
    {
      "question": "enclosed in or as if in a box",
      "answer": "boxed"
    },
    {
      "question": "liable to be accused, or cause for such liability",
      "answer": "chargeable"
    },
    {
      "question": "a thin porridge (usually oatmeal or cornmeal)  ",
      "answer": "gruel"
    },
    {
      "question": "in such a manner as to make something clearly evident",
      "answer": "pointedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of circumcising",
      "answer": "circumcision"
    },
    {
      "question": "become wider",
      "answer": "dilate"
    },
    {
      "question": "brilliant or conspicuous success or effect",
      "answer": "eclat"
    },
    {
      "question": "crested largely blue bird  ",
      "answer": "jay"
    },
    {
      "question": "spotlessly clean and fresh",
      "answer": "unsullied"
    },
    {
      "question": "crack and acquire the appearance of alligator hide, as from weathering or improper application",
      "answer": "alligator"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of an idea or opinion) formed beforehand",
      "answer": "preconceived"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pedigreed animal of unmixed lineage",
      "answer": "thoroughbred"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pupil who lives at school during term time  ",
      "answer": "boarder"
    },
    {
      "question": "writing done with a typewriter  ",
      "answer": "typing"
    },
    {
      "question": "a remote and undeveloped area  ",
      "answer": "backwoods"
    },
    {
      "question": "a laborer who is obliged to do menial work  ",
      "answer": "drudge"
    },
    {
      "question": "offensive to the mind",
      "answer": "abhorrent"
    },
    {
      "question": "anticipating with confidence of fulfillment  ",
      "answer": "anticipation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being false or untrue",
      "answer": "falsity"
    },
    {
      "question": "the killing of a human being by another human being  ",
      "answer": "homicide"
    },
    {
      "question": "getting two things to correspond",
      "answer": "reconciliation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a brushing or rustling sound  ",
      "answer": "swish"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by a lack of openness (especially about one's actions or purposes)  ",
      "answer": "closeness"
    },
    {
      "question": "affirm or declare as an attribute or quality of",
      "answer": "predicate"
    },
    {
      "question": "fool or hoax",
      "answer": "gull"
    },
    {
      "question": "over an extended time",
      "answer": "longitudinal"
    },
    {
      "question": "hunting with dogs (usually greyhounds) that are trained to chase game (such as hares) by sight instead of by scent  ",
      "answer": "coursing"
    },
    {
      "question": "a deep narrow steep-sided valley (especially one formed by running water)  ",
      "answer": "ravine"
    },
    {
      "question": "an official at a baseball game  ",
      "answer": "umpire"
    },
    {
      "question": "accept people into an exclusive society or group, usually with some rite",
      "answer": "initiate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the 4th letter of the Greek alphabet  ",
      "answer": "delta"
    },
    {
      "question": "the dignity or rank or position of a king  ",
      "answer": "kingship"
    },
    {
      "question": "not forbearing",
      "answer": "unsparing"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to bring discredit or disrepute",
      "answer": "discreditable"
    },
    {
      "question": "feel extreme happiness or elation  ",
      "answer": "exult"
    },
    {
      "question": "prudence in avoiding waste  ",
      "answer": "frugality"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman skilled in aiding the delivery of babies  ",
      "answer": "midwife"
    },
    {
      "question": "disgust so strong it makes you feel sick  ",
      "answer": "nausea"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing little emotion",
      "answer": "phlegmatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking aesthetic or social taste  ",
      "answer": "tasteless"
    },
    {
      "question": "not easily irritated",
      "answer": "equable"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by or causing boisterous merriment or convulsive laughter",
      "answer": "hilarious"
    },
    {
      "question": "restrain with fetters  ",
      "answer": "fetter"
    },
    {
      "question": "a booth where a priest sits to hear confessions  ",
      "answer": "confessional"
    },
    {
      "question": "wood heaped for burning a dead body as a funeral rite  ",
      "answer": "pyre"
    },
    {
      "question": "a window in a roof to admit daylight  ",
      "answer": "skylight"
    },
    {
      "question": "hard to control",
      "answer": "unmanageable"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of turning inside out  ",
      "answer": "inversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large burial chamber, usually above ground  ",
      "answer": "mausoleum"
    },
    {
      "question": "any commodity of intermediate quality or size (especially when coarse particles of ground wheat are mixed with bran)  ",
      "answer": "middling"
    },
    {
      "question": "building material used in laying floors  ",
      "answer": "flooring"
    },
    {
      "question": "a compact breed of harness horse  ",
      "answer": "hackney"
    },
    {
      "question": "an alternative that is not available  ",
      "answer": "impossibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "excessively mournful  ",
      "answer": "lugubrious"
    },
    {
      "question": "an ache localized in or around a tooth  ",
      "answer": "toothache"
    },
    {
      "question": "a ludicrous folly",
      "answer": "absurdity"
    },
    {
      "question": "prove to be false",
      "answer": "disprove"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of searching for food and provisions  ",
      "answer": "foraging"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to be a concomitant  ",
      "answer": "necessitate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the activity of making portraits  ",
      "answer": "portraiture"
    },
    {
      "question": "an aperture or hole that opens into a bodily cavity",
      "answer": "orifice"
    },
    {
      "question": "electro-acoustic transducer that vibrates to receive or produce sound waves  ",
      "answer": "diaphragm"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a fitful manner",
      "answer": "fitfully"
    },
    {
      "question": "a surface coating for ceramics or porcelain  ",
      "answer": "luster"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling a serpent in form",
      "answer": "serpentine"
    },
    {
      "question": "gather snails",
      "answer": "snail"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the appearance of being real but lacking capacity to function",
      "answer": "dummy"
    },
    {
      "question": "administer an oil or ointment to ",
      "answer": "anoint"
    },
    {
      "question": "treat by incorporating fat",
      "answer": "curry"
    },
    {
      "question": "lessen the strength or flavor of a solution or mixture",
      "answer": "dilute"
    },
    {
      "question": "with pretense or intention to deceive",
      "answer": "professedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the bed on which a person dies  ",
      "answer": "deathbed"
    },
    {
      "question": "not showing due care or attention",
      "answer": "inattentive"
    },
    {
      "question": "not appealing to the senses",
      "answer": "unattractive"
    },
    {
      "question": "a member of a conspiracy  ",
      "answer": "conspirator"
    },
    {
      "question": "(poetry) painful grief  ",
      "answer": "dolor"
    },
    {
      "question": "a blue to grey green mineral consisting of copper aluminum phosphate",
      "answer": "turquoise"
    },
    {
      "question": "the convent of a community of nuns  ",
      "answer": "nunnery"
    },
    {
      "question": "a conduit through which water flows  ",
      "answer": "watercourse"
    },
    {
      "question": "projecting part of a rampart or other fortification  ",
      "answer": "bastion"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a hideous manner",
      "answer": "hideously"
    },
    {
      "question": "reject outright and bluntly",
      "answer": "rebuff"
    },
    {
      "question": "with respect to dramatic value",
      "answer": "dramatically"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of entering",
      "answer": "entree"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or characteristic of opera  ",
      "answer": "operatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "resolute adherence to your own ideas or desires  ",
      "answer": "stubbornness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a thin strip of leather",
      "answer": "thong"
    },
    {
      "question": "stab or urge on as if with a pointed stick  ",
      "answer": "goad"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of a class of solid or semisolid viscous substances obtained either as exudations from certain plants or prepared by polymerization of simple molecules  ",
      "answer": "resin"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a sarcastic manner",
      "answer": "sarcastically"
    },
    {
      "question": "a song or hymn of mourning composed or performed as a memorial to a dead person  ",
      "answer": "dirge"
    },
    {
      "question": "slowly and broadly  ",
      "answer": "largo"
    },
    {
      "question": "self-propelled movement  ",
      "answer": "locomotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a clearly noticeable manner",
      "answer": "markedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "shell containing lead pellets that explodes in flight  ",
      "answer": "shrapnel"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking civility or good manners",
      "answer": "uncivil"
    },
    {
      "question": "temporary cessation or suspension  ",
      "answer": "abeyance"
    },
    {
      "question": "unaffected by strong emotion or prejudice",
      "answer": "dispassionate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mathematical notation indicating the number of times a quantity is multiplied by itself  ",
      "answer": "exponent"
    },
    {
      "question": "a building where people go to eat  ",
      "answer": "restaurant"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a sparse manner",
      "answer": "sparsely"
    },
    {
      "question": "an additional payment (or other remuneration) to employees as a means of increasing output  ",
      "answer": "bonus"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being changeable and variable  ",
      "answer": "inconstancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "remaining in an original state",
      "answer": "unaltered"
    },
    {
      "question": "a musician who plays the violin  ",
      "answer": "violinist"
    },
    {
      "question": "an angel of the second order whose gift is knowledge",
      "answer": "cherub"
    },
    {
      "question": "suffer from sudden painful contraction of a muscle  ",
      "answer": "cramp"
    },
    {
      "question": "passing from a more complex to a simpler biological form  ",
      "answer": "degeneration"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by good fortune",
      "answer": "felicitous"
    },
    {
      "question": "an attack of hysteria  ",
      "answer": "hysterics"
    },
    {
      "question": "pen where racehorses are saddled and paraded before a race  ",
      "answer": "paddock"
    },
    {
      "question": "held from above",
      "answer": "pendent"
    },
    {
      "question": "cast off",
      "answer": "disown"
    },
    {
      "question": "physically or spiritually homeless or deprived of security",
      "answer": "dispossessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of coming (or going) out",
      "answer": "egress"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of adding extraneous decorations to something  ",
      "answer": "ornamentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who risks losses for the possibility of considerable gains  ",
      "answer": "speculator"
    },
    {
      "question": "a speech disorder involving hesitations and involuntary repetitions of certain sounds  ",
      "answer": "stammer"
    },
    {
      "question": "either of two bean-shaped excretory organs that filter wastes (especially urea) from the blood and excrete them and water in urine",
      "answer": "kidney"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of especially horses) having a brownish coat thickly sprinkled with white or grey",
      "answer": "roan"
    },
    {
      "question": "take to task",
      "answer": "admonish"
    },
    {
      "question": "make into a puddle",
      "answer": "muddle"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who pays more attention to formal rules and book learning than they merit  ",
      "answer": "pedant"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a rational manner",
      "answer": "rationally"
    },
    {
      "question": "formed or united into a whole  ",
      "answer": "incorporate"
    },
    {
      "question": "befitting a monk",
      "answer": "monkish"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a harmonious manner",
      "answer": "harmoniously"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a heroic manner",
      "answer": "heroically"
    },
    {
      "question": "idle or foolish and irrelevant talk  ",
      "answer": "prate"
    },
    {
      "question": "transgressing a moral or divine law",
      "answer": "sinning"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the manner of human beings",
      "answer": "humanly"
    },
    {
      "question": "not safe from attack  ",
      "answer": "insecure"
    },
    {
      "question": "have a strong desire or urge to do something",
      "answer": "itch"
    },
    {
      "question": "the basic unit of money in Western Samoa  ",
      "answer": "tala"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sequence of powerful leaders in the same family  ",
      "answer": "dynasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "open and observable",
      "answer": "overt"
    },
    {
      "question": "a long and often twisted hot red pepper  ",
      "answer": "cayenne"
    },
    {
      "question": "at an opportune time",
      "answer": "opportunely"
    },
    {
      "question": "be a signal for or a symptom of",
      "answer": "bespeak"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking the properties characteristic of living organisms  ",
      "answer": "inorganic"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter while panting, as if out of breath  ",
      "answer": "pant"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of numerous plants of the family Compositae and especially of the genera Carduus and Cirsium and Onopordum having prickly-edged leaves  ",
      "answer": "thistle"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who takes photographs professionally  ",
      "answer": "photographer"
    },
    {
      "question": "a roof in the form of a dome  ",
      "answer": "cupola"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being in or of the future  ",
      "answer": "futurity"
    },
    {
      "question": "not excusable  ",
      "answer": "inexcusable"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a light, metallic sound",
      "answer": "ting"
    },
    {
      "question": "an agent who conducts an auction  ",
      "answer": "auctioneer"
    },
    {
      "question": "leave one's country of residence for a new one",
      "answer": "emigrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a journey by a large group to escape from a hostile environment  ",
      "answer": "exodus"
    },
    {
      "question": "to compel or deter by or as if by threats  ",
      "answer": "intimidate"
    },
    {
      "question": "pocket-sized paperback book  ",
      "answer": "pocketbook"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to turn away from a previous or expected course",
      "answer": "deviate"
    },
    {
      "question": "exceedingly harmful  ",
      "answer": "baneful"
    },
    {
      "question": "a specialist in geology  ",
      "answer": "geologist"
    },
    {
      "question": "a reproduction of a written record (e.g. of a legal or school record)  ",
      "answer": "transcript"
    },
    {
      "question": "water travel for pleasure  ",
      "answer": "boating"
    },
    {
      "question": "heedful of potential consequences",
      "answer": "circumspect"
    },
    {
      "question": "the basic unit of money in Armenia  ",
      "answer": "dram"
    },
    {
      "question": "direct carefully and safely",
      "answer": "navigate"
    },
    {
      "question": "an exile who flees for safety  ",
      "answer": "refugee"
    },
    {
      "question": "thrusting inward",
      "answer": "intrusive"
    },
    {
      "question": "lack of proportion",
      "answer": "disproportion"
    },
    {
      "question": "a party of people assembled in the evening (usually at a private house)  ",
      "answer": "soiree"
    },
    {
      "question": "a United States coin worth one tenth of a dollar  ",
      "answer": "dime"
    },
    {
      "question": "the process of purifying a liquid by boiling it and condensing its vapors  ",
      "answer": "distillation"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to domineer  ",
      "answer": "domineering"
    },
    {
      "question": "move down on as if in an attack",
      "answer": "pounce"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or involving or preoccupied with doctrine",
      "answer": "doctrinal"
    },
    {
      "question": "laugh at with contempt and derision",
      "answer": "jeer"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing lack of certainty",
      "answer": "uncertainly"
    },
    {
      "question": "being or suggesting a cavern",
      "answer": "cavernous"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to exalt",
      "answer": "ennobling"
    },
    {
      "question": "not likely to be rewarded",
      "answer": "thankless"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by a lack of interest",
      "answer": "apathetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a brass musical instrument with a brilliant tone",
      "answer": "cornet"
    },
    {
      "question": "not passionate",
      "answer": "passionless"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a diagonal manner",
      "answer": "diagonally"
    },
    {
      "question": "in ignorance",
      "answer": "ignorantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking the ability or skill to perform effectively",
      "answer": "ineffective"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to rural matters",
      "answer": "agrarian"
    },
    {
      "question": "the condition of being impure  ",
      "answer": "impurity"
    },
    {
      "question": "board that provides a flat surface on which artists mix paints and the range of colors used  ",
      "answer": "palette"
    },
    {
      "question": "covered with or as if with soot",
      "answer": "sooty"
    },
    {
      "question": "no longer in use",
      "answer": "disused"
    },
    {
      "question": "existing as or having characteristics of a gas",
      "answer": "gaseous"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone employed to clean and maintain a building  ",
      "answer": "janitor"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing difficulty in breathing especially through lack of fresh air and presence of heat",
      "answer": "smothering"
    },
    {
      "question": "a party favor consisting of a paper roll (usually containing candy or a small favor) that pops when pulled at both ends  ",
      "answer": "cracker"
    },
    {
      "question": "allowing slavery",
      "answer": "slaveholding"
    },
    {
      "question": "a guest cabin  ",
      "answer": "stateroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a vacant manner",
      "answer": "vacantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who supervises the actors and directs the action in the production of a show  ",
      "answer": "director"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a gruff manner",
      "answer": "gruffly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a flammable hydrocarbon oil used as fuel in lamps and heaters  ",
      "answer": "kerosene"
    },
    {
      "question": "an unhealthy and compulsive preoccupation with something or someone  ",
      "answer": "obsession"
    },
    {
      "question": "treated irreverently or sacrilegiously  ",
      "answer": "profaned"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a covert manner",
      "answer": "covertly"
    },
    {
      "question": "inactivity of liquids",
      "answer": "stagnation"
    },
    {
      "question": "charming in a childlike or naive way  ",
      "answer": "winsome"
    },
    {
      "question": "belonging to or on or near the back or upper surface of an animal or organ or part",
      "answer": "dorsal"
    },
    {
      "question": "subjugate by imposing troops  ",
      "answer": "dragoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "of persons",
      "answer": "exploited"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a shrill voice",
      "answer": "shrilly"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a superficial manner",
      "answer": "superficially"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being a widow who has not remarried  ",
      "answer": "widowhood"
    },
    {
      "question": "defeat soundly",
      "answer": "demolish"
    },
    {
      "question": "catch sight of  ",
      "answer": "descry"
    },
    {
      "question": "the wide part of a river where it nears the sea",
      "answer": "estuary"
    },
    {
      "question": "gush forth in a sudden stream or jet",
      "answer": "spurt"
    },
    {
      "question": "a ship that has been wrecked and abandoned  ",
      "answer": "hulk"
    },
    {
      "question": "stimulate to remember",
      "answer": "jog"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or having the characteristics of journalism",
      "answer": "journalistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the excitement and emotional appeal of melodrama",
      "answer": "melodramatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing skill and sensitivity in dealing with people",
      "answer": "tactful"
    },
    {
      "question": " connecting two nonadjacent corners of a plane figure or any two corners of a solid that are not in the same face",
      "answer": "diagonal"
    },
    {
      "question": "by open declaration",
      "answer": "avowedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "not leading to a definite ending or result",
      "answer": "indeterminate"
    },
    {
      "question": "unwilling to spend",
      "answer": "stingy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being appealing in a delicate or graceful way (of a girl or young woman)  ",
      "answer": "prettiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a judgment by a higher court that the judgment of a lower court was incorrect and should be set aside  ",
      "answer": "reversal"
    },
    {
      "question": "rise and move, as in waves or billows",
      "answer": "billow"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mattress filled with straw or a pad made of quilts",
      "answer": "pallet"
    },
    {
      "question": "a square dance of 5 or more figures for 4 or more couples  ",
      "answer": "quadrille"
    },
    {
      "question": "a storm resulting from strong rising air currents",
      "answer": "thunderstorm"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who investigates  ",
      "answer": "investigator"
    },
    {
      "question": "make more precise or increase the discriminatory powers of",
      "answer": "refine"
    },
    {
      "question": "occurring by happy chance",
      "answer": "fortuitous"
    },
    {
      "question": "slightly salty (especially from containing a mixture of seawater and fresh water)",
      "answer": "brackish"
    },
    {
      "question": "a source of materials to nourish the body  ",
      "answer": "nutriment"
    },
    {
      "question": "large globular fruit having many seeds with juicy red pulp in a tough brownish-red rind  ",
      "answer": "pomegranate"
    },
    {
      "question": "made clean by scrubbing",
      "answer": "scrubbed"
    },
    {
      "question": "keep score, as in games  ",
      "answer": "tally"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an unsteady manner",
      "answer": "unsteadily"
    },
    {
      "question": "a clique (often secret) that seeks power usually through intrigue  ",
      "answer": "cabal"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various fruit of cucurbitaceous vines including: muskmelons",
      "answer": "melon"
    },
    {
      "question": "break up into splinters or slivers",
      "answer": "splinter"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who takes vengeance  ",
      "answer": "avenger"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of remaining calm and seeming not to care",
      "answer": "nonchalance"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing great physical or mental suffering",
      "answer": "racking"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who contributes (or promises to contribute) a sum of money  ",
      "answer": "subscriber"
    },
    {
      "question": "restaurant in a factory",
      "answer": "canteen"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of enlisting (as in a military service)  ",
      "answer": "enlistment"
    },
    {
      "question": "the 12th letter of the Greek alphabet  ",
      "answer": "mu"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman sorcerer  ",
      "answer": "sorceress"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or adorned with tufts",
      "answer": "tufted"
    },
    {
      "question": "having utility often to the exclusion of values",
      "answer": "utilitarian"
    },
    {
      "question": "in keeping with the nature of the Bible or its times or people",
      "answer": "biblical"
    },
    {
      "question": "derive by reason",
      "answer": "elicit"
    },
    {
      "question": "sit or let sit in boiling water so as to extract the flavor",
      "answer": "brew"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of being changed in substance as if by alchemy",
      "answer": "convertible"
    },
    {
      "question": "cake flavored with ginger  ",
      "answer": "gingerbread"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to fabrics or fabric making",
      "answer": "textile"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to move apart in different directions  ",
      "answer": "divergent"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking definition or definite content",
      "answer": "nebulous"
    },
    {
      "question": "mutual exchange of commercial or other privileges  ",
      "answer": "reciprocity"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a sleepy manner",
      "answer": "sleepily"
    },
    {
      "question": "a witch doctor who practices conjury  ",
      "answer": "conjurer"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of speaking contemptuously of  ",
      "answer": "disparagement"
    },
    {
      "question": "attach with a hinge  ",
      "answer": "hinge"
    },
    {
      "question": "strong highly flavored sweet liquor usually drunk after a meal  ",
      "answer": "liqueur"
    },
    {
      "question": "beaklike projection of the anterior part of the head of certain insects such as e.g. weevils  ",
      "answer": "snout"
    },
    {
      "question": "having turned bad  ",
      "answer": "soured"
    },
    {
      "question": "acceptance as true or valid  ",
      "answer": "acceptation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a short introductory essay preceding the text of a book  ",
      "answer": "foreword"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who tempts others",
      "answer": "tempter"
    },
    {
      "question": "(astronomy) the rising of a star above the horizon  ",
      "answer": "ascension"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who sews",
      "answer": "sewer"
    },
    {
      "question": "structure forming the transverse part of a cruciform church",
      "answer": "transept"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of a state or an event) taking place without something specified occurring at the same time",
      "answer": "unaccompanied"
    },
    {
      "question": "petty or reluctant in giving or spending",
      "answer": "grudging"
    },
    {
      "question": "not merited",
      "answer": "unmerited"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of being recognized  ",
      "answer": "recognizable"
    },
    {
      "question": "formerly a contemptuous term of address to an inferior man or boy",
      "answer": "sirrah"
    },
    {
      "question": "an excerpt cut from a newspaper or magazine",
      "answer": "clipping"
    },
    {
      "question": "hard fat around the kidneys and loins in beef and sheep  ",
      "answer": "suet"
    },
    {
      "question": "fortification consisting of a strong fence made of stakes driven into the ground  ",
      "answer": "palisade"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or resembling skin  ",
      "answer": "skinny"
    },
    {
      "question": "affectedly genteel  ",
      "answer": "grandiose"
    },
    {
      "question": "any igneous rock with crystals embedded in a finer groundmass of minerals  ",
      "answer": "porphyry"
    },
    {
      "question": "the office of a regent  ",
      "answer": "regency"
    },
    {
      "question": "a feeling of lack of concern  ",
      "answer": "unconcern"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to become loose",
      "answer": "untie"
    },
    {
      "question": "a traveler going on a trip  ",
      "answer": "wayfarer"
    },
    {
      "question": "any violent blow  ",
      "answer": "concussion"
    },
    {
      "question": "an almost pleasurable sensation of fright",
      "answer": "frisson"
    },
    {
      "question": "a gauze fabric with an extremely fine texture  ",
      "answer": "gossamer"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a tame manner",
      "answer": "tamely"
    },
    {
      "question": "offensively self-assured or given to exercising usually unwarranted power",
      "answer": "autocratic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a meeting of spiritualists",
      "answer": "seance"
    },
    {
      "question": "put forth and grow sprouts or shoots",
      "answer": "sprout"
    },
    {
      "question": "defiantly aggressive",
      "answer": "truculent"
    },
    {
      "question": "the labor of taking a load of something off of or out of a vehicle or ship or container etc.  ",
      "answer": "unloading"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of preventing something from occurring",
      "answer": "averting"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove by cutting",
      "answer": "excise"
    },
    {
      "question": "the substance of a living cell (including cytoplasm and nucleus)  ",
      "answer": "protoplasm"
    },
    {
      "question": "move along on skates",
      "answer": "skate"
    },
    {
      "question": "in bed  ",
      "answer": "abed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a low metal guard to confine falling coals to a hearth  ",
      "answer": "fender"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mode of conducting legal and parliamentary proceedings  ",
      "answer": "procedure"
    },
    {
      "question": "enameled or lacquered metalware (usually gilded and elaborately painted)",
      "answer": "tole"
    },
    {
      "question": "a brightly printed and glazed cotton fabric  ",
      "answer": "chintz"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ropes in the rigging of a ship  ",
      "answer": "cordage"
    },
    {
      "question": "young cow  ",
      "answer": "heifer"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property of having a relatively great size  ",
      "answer": "largeness"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the surface burned quickly with intense heat",
      "answer": "seared"
    },
    {
      "question": "the condition of being deprived of oxygen (as by having breathing stopped)",
      "answer": "suffocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of threatening evil  ",
      "answer": "malevolence"
    },
    {
      "question": "manipulate the mouse of a computer  ",
      "answer": "mouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who travels about selling his wares (as on the streets or at carnivals)  ",
      "answer": "peddler"
    },
    {
      "question": "settle down or stay, as if on a roost  ",
      "answer": "roost"
    },
    {
      "question": "a competition at which a champion is chosen  ",
      "answer": "championship"
    },
    {
      "question": "undergo development or evolution",
      "answer": "evolve"
    },
    {
      "question": "yard consisting of an outdoor area for children's play  ",
      "answer": "playground"
    },
    {
      "question": "covered or furnished with tiles",
      "answer": "tiled"
    },
    {
      "question": "an expression of sympathy with another's grief",
      "answer": "condolence"
    },
    {
      "question": "suggestive of companionship",
      "answer": "companionable"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a sparse or scanty way",
      "answer": "scantily"
    },
    {
      "question": "take out or up with or as if with a scoop",
      "answer": "scoop"
    },
    {
      "question": "produced by a wildly fanciful imagination",
      "answer": "chimerical"
    },
    {
      "question": "the concluding part of any performance  ",
      "answer": "finale"
    },
    {
      "question": "tanned skin of a sheep with the fleece left on",
      "answer": "sheepskin"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a high sound typical of glass",
      "answer": "clink"
    },
    {
      "question": "a castrated tomcat  ",
      "answer": "gib"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ship that carries the commander of a fleet and flies his flag  ",
      "answer": "flagship"
    },
    {
      "question": "insert or squeeze tightly between two people or objects",
      "answer": "sandwich"
    },
    {
      "question": "the playing of a game of tenpins or duckpins etc  ",
      "answer": "bowling"
    },
    {
      "question": "a privately owned warship commissioned to prey on the commercial shipping or warships of an enemy nation  ",
      "answer": "privateer"
    },
    {
      "question": "temporarily and conditionally",
      "answer": "provisionally"
    },
    {
      "question": "imparting strength and vitality",
      "answer": "invigorating"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of not being open or truthful",
      "answer": "insincerity"
    },
    {
      "question": "act of removing from office or employment  ",
      "answer": "displacement"
    },
    {
      "question": "a device for making soundings  ",
      "answer": "sounder"
    },
    {
      "question": "the part of the sea that can be seen from the shore and is beyond the anchoring area",
      "answer": "offing"
    },
    {
      "question": "defining rights and duties as opposed to giving the rules by which rights and duties are established",
      "answer": "substantive"
    },
    {
      "question": "a representation by picture or portraiture  ",
      "answer": "depicting"
    },
    {
      "question": "be wide open",
      "answer": "gape"
    },
    {
      "question": "the head of a branch of an organized crime syndicate  ",
      "answer": "capo"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a circuit or device that represents magnitudes in digits",
      "answer": "digital"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of constructing something (as a piece of machinery)  ",
      "answer": "fabrication"
    },
    {
      "question": "the mathematics of generalized arithmetical operations  ",
      "answer": "algebra"
    },
    {
      "question": "without intention",
      "answer": "unintentionally"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking sincerity",
      "answer": "insincere"
    },
    {
      "question": "adapt",
      "answer": "put"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to break into many pieces",
      "answer": "shatter"
    },
    {
      "question": "climb awkwardly, as if by scrambling  ",
      "answer": "clamber"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of giving displeasure",
      "answer": "unpleasantness"
    },
    {
      "question": "surrounded entirely or almost entirely by land",
      "answer": "landlocked"
    },
    {
      "question": "relieve temporarily  ",
      "answer": "reprieve"
    },
    {
      "question": "lawfulness by virtue of conformity to a legal statute  ",
      "answer": "legality"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to an oracle",
      "answer": "oracular"
    },
    {
      "question": "a straw hat with a tall crown and broad brim",
      "answer": "sombrero"
    },
    {
      "question": "used of plant stock or scions",
      "answer": "uncongenial"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an unjust or unfair manner",
      "answer": "wrongfully"
    },
    {
      "question": "unsatisfactoriness by virtue of being inadequate  ",
      "answer": "inadequacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who is an active supporter and advocate  ",
      "answer": "promoter"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being spontaneous and coming from natural feelings without constraint",
      "answer": "spontaneity"
    },
    {
      "question": "a state of violent disturbance and disorder (as in politics or social conditions generally)",
      "answer": "turbulence"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling paste in color",
      "answer": "pasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a sulky manner",
      "answer": "sulkily"
    },
    {
      "question": "having ceased to exist or live",
      "answer": "defunct"
    },
    {
      "question": "(folklore) a giant who likes to eat human beings  ",
      "answer": "ogre"
    },
    {
      "question": "a strong slender smooth-haired dog of Spanish origin having a white coat with brown or black patches",
      "answer": "pointer"
    },
    {
      "question": "administer baptism to",
      "answer": "baptize"
    },
    {
      "question": "convert into direct current",
      "answer": "rectify"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being good looking and attractive  ",
      "answer": "comeliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "reproduced or made to resemble",
      "answer": "simulated"
    },
    {
      "question": "the size of a book whose pages are made by folding a sheet of paper three times to form eight leaves  ",
      "answer": "octavo"
    },
    {
      "question": "a state of mental disturbance and disorientation  ",
      "answer": "derangement"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of not moving  ",
      "answer": "immobility"
    },
    {
      "question": "improper or excessive use",
      "answer": "misuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "carbonated drink with fruit syrup and a little phosphoric acid  ",
      "answer": "phosphate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a high-pitched noise resembling a human cry",
      "answer": "screech"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking spontaneity or originality or individuality",
      "answer": "stereotyped"
    },
    {
      "question": "not yet opened or unsealed",
      "answer": "unopened"
    },
    {
      "question": "a vessel made of material that does not melt easily",
      "answer": "crucible"
    },
    {
      "question": "tediously repetitious or lacking in variety",
      "answer": "humdrum"
    },
    {
      "question": "a request for payment",
      "answer": "notification"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a questionably unusual manner",
      "answer": "queerly"
    },
    {
      "question": "an authoritative command or request  ",
      "answer": "behest"
    },
    {
      "question": "light automatic rifle  ",
      "answer": "carbine"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic of the time of chivalry and knighthood in the Middle Ages",
      "answer": "chivalric"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property possessed by the curving of a line or surface  ",
      "answer": "curvature"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an approving manner",
      "answer": "approvingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "in coarse pieces",
      "answer": "coarsely"
    },
    {
      "question": "an impression in a surface (as made by a blow)  ",
      "answer": "dent"
    },
    {
      "question": "(spatial sense) without bounds",
      "answer": "endlessly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large square-rigged sailing ship with three or more masts",
      "answer": "galleon"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of catching fire spontaneously or causing fires or burning readily",
      "answer": "incendiary"
    },
    {
      "question": "small fishing boat rigged with one or more lugsails  ",
      "answer": "lugger"
    },
    {
      "question": "an extravagant comedy in which action is more salient than characterization  ",
      "answer": "melodrama"
    },
    {
      "question": "the final game of a double header  ",
      "answer": "nightcap"
    },
    {
      "question": "capture again",
      "answer": "recapture"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter a hoarse sound, like a raven  ",
      "answer": "croak"
    },
    {
      "question": "a short simple song (or the words of a poem intended to be sung)  ",
      "answer": "ditty"
    },
    {
      "question": "a line (as on a vessel or ruler) that marks a measurement",
      "answer": "graduation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of hearty sincerity  ",
      "answer": "heartiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small gate in the rear of a fort or castle  ",
      "answer": "postern"
    },
    {
      "question": "propel with a rocket  ",
      "answer": "rocket"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a common center",
      "answer": "concentric"
    },
    {
      "question": "an inclination or desire",
      "answer": "devices"
    },
    {
      "question": "an ideal instance",
      "answer": "paragon"
    },
    {
      "question": "emitting light without appreciable heat as by slow oxidation of phosphorous",
      "answer": "phosphorescent"
    },
    {
      "question": "desiring or striving for recognition or advancement  ",
      "answer": "aspirant"
    },
    {
      "question": "preliminary preparation as a basis or foundation",
      "answer": "groundwork"
    },
    {
      "question": "having deserted a cause or principle",
      "answer": "recreant"
    },
    {
      "question": "luggage consisting of a small case with a flat bottom and (usually) a shoulder strap  ",
      "answer": "satchel"
    },
    {
      "question": "consciously perceiving",
      "answer": "sentient"
    },
    {
      "question": "leaking out slowly  ",
      "answer": "oozing"
    },
    {
      "question": "arranged according to size  ",
      "answer": "sorted"
    },
    {
      "question": "not righteous",
      "answer": "unrighteous"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being degenerate in mental or moral qualities  ",
      "answer": "degeneracy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the condition or quality of being a virgin  ",
      "answer": "virginity"
    },
    {
      "question": "past due",
      "answer": "delinquent"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of constituting a political unity out of a number of separate states or colonies or provinces so that each member retains the management of its internal affairs  ",
      "answer": "federation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a title given to rulers or other important people in Asian countries  ",
      "answer": "khan"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a puddle by splashing water  ",
      "answer": "puddle"
    },
    {
      "question": "respiratory organ of aquatic animals that breathe oxygen dissolved in water  ",
      "answer": "gill"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking grace",
      "answer": "graceless"
    },
    {
      "question": "the final point in a process  ",
      "answer": "resultant"
    },
    {
      "question": "terminate the employment of",
      "answer": "displace"
    },
    {
      "question": "an acronym for emissions of light and very low frequency perturbations due to electromagnetic pulse sources",
      "answer": "elves"
    },
    {
      "question": "change the inherent purpose or function of something",
      "answer": "pervert"
    },
    {
      "question": "lure or entrap with or as if with a decoy  ",
      "answer": "decoy"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to feel shame",
      "answer": "humiliate"
    },
    {
      "question": "an act of atrocious cruelty  ",
      "answer": "atrocity"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person of subnormal intelligence  ",
      "answer": "idiot"
    },
    {
      "question": "arranged in a line  ",
      "answer": "lineal"
    },
    {
      "question": "a place of inviolable privacy",
      "answer": "sanctum"
    },
    {
      "question": "to move in a twisting or contorted motion, (especially when struggling)",
      "answer": "writhe"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic life processes and phenomena of living organisms",
      "answer": "biology"
    },
    {
      "question": "become tight or tighter",
      "answer": "tighten"
    },
    {
      "question": "the science of planting and caring for forests and the management of growing timber  ",
      "answer": "forestry"
    },
    {
      "question": "(folklore) a small grotesque supernatural creature that makes trouble for human beings  ",
      "answer": "goblin"
    },
    {
      "question": "at a very fast tempo (faster than allegro)  ",
      "answer": "presto"
    },
    {
      "question": "(card games) the act of taking a trick with a trump when unable to follow suit  ",
      "answer": "ruff"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by up-to-dateness in dress and manners",
      "answer": "dapper"
    },
    {
      "question": "the back side of the neck  ",
      "answer": "nape"
    },
    {
      "question": "not worth considering",
      "answer": "negligible"
    },
    {
      "question": "toward heaven",
      "answer": "heavenward"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quantity that can be contained in the arms  ",
      "answer": "armful"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking hair on the face",
      "answer": "beardless"
    },
    {
      "question": "a piece of land held under the feudal system  ",
      "answer": "fief"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being total and complete",
      "answer": "entirety"
    },
    {
      "question": "fighting",
      "answer": "hostilities"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an imprudent manner",
      "answer": "imprudently"
    },
    {
      "question": "an informal use of the Latin word for mother",
      "answer": "mater"
    },
    {
      "question": "lack of sophistication or worldliness  ",
      "answer": "naivete"
    },
    {
      "question": "a stone coffin (usually bearing sculpture or inscriptions)  ",
      "answer": "sarcophagus"
    },
    {
      "question": "like the sound of rapidly vibrating wings  ",
      "answer": "whirring"
    },
    {
      "question": "a traveler to a distant land (especially one who travels by sea)  ",
      "answer": "voyager"
    },
    {
      "question": "pounded or hit repeatedly by storms or adversities  ",
      "answer": "buffeted"
    },
    {
      "question": "an informal use of the Latin word for father",
      "answer": "pater"
    },
    {
      "question": "formerly, the eldest son of the King of France and direct heir to the throne  ",
      "answer": "dauphin"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pressing or urgent situation",
      "answer": "exigency"
    },
    {
      "question": "extremely wicked",
      "answer": "nefarious"
    },
    {
      "question": "written in abbreviated or symbolic form",
      "answer": "shorthand"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various freshwater fish of the family Cyprinidae  ",
      "answer": "carp"
    },
    {
      "question": "(physics) the intermolecular force that holds together the molecules in a solid or liquid  ",
      "answer": "cohesion"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or used in exercises intended to develop strength and agility",
      "answer": "gymnastic"
    },
    {
      "question": "suggestive of an idyll",
      "answer": "idyllic"
    },
    {
      "question": "opposite in nature or effect or relation to another quantity ",
      "answer": "inverse"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a sumptuous and opulent manner",
      "answer": "sumptuously"
    },
    {
      "question": "hoofed mammal of mountains of Eurasia having upright horns with backward-hooked tips  ",
      "answer": "chamois"
    },
    {
      "question": "a translucent mineral consisting of hydrated silica of variable color",
      "answer": "opal"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the body covered or partially covered with thin horny plates, as some fish and reptiles  ",
      "answer": "scaly"
    },
    {
      "question": "burst or force (a hole) into something  ",
      "answer": "stave"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various religions other than Christianity or Judaism or Islamism  ",
      "answer": "paganism"
    },
    {
      "question": "a regional dialect of a language (especially French)",
      "answer": "patois"
    },
    {
      "question": "draw in (air)",
      "answer": "inhale"
    },
    {
      "question": "express discontent  ",
      "answer": "repine"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of increasing the wealth or prestige or power or scope of something",
      "answer": "aggrandizement"
    },
    {
      "question": "cleverly amusing in tone",
      "answer": "bantering"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being a beggar or mendicant",
      "answer": "beggary"
    },
    {
      "question": "caused by or evidencing a mentally disturbed condition",
      "answer": "pathological"
    },
    {
      "question": "very spiny and dense evergreen shrub with fragrant golden-yellow flowers",
      "answer": "gorse"
    },
    {
      "question": "travel back and forth between two points  ",
      "answer": "shuttle"
    },
    {
      "question": "fill by packing tightly",
      "answer": "stow"
    },
    {
      "question": "used to wrap around pipes or boilers or laid in attics to prevent loss of heat  ",
      "answer": "lagging"
    },
    {
      "question": "studies of the rules for forming admissible sentences  ",
      "answer": "syntax"
    },
    {
      "question": "(psychoanalysis) the process whereby emotions are passed on or displaced from one person to another",
      "answer": "transference"
    },
    {
      "question": "a misleading falsehood  ",
      "answer": "misrepresentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or pertaining to tactic or tactics",
      "answer": "tactical"
    },
    {
      "question": "a symmetrical arrangement of the parts of a thing  ",
      "answer": "conformation"
    },
    {
      "question": "from a financial point of view",
      "answer": "financially"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter while crying  ",
      "answer": "blubber"
    },
    {
      "question": "dressed in a habit",
      "answer": "habited"
    },
    {
      "question": "British breed of large heavy draft horse  ",
      "answer": "shire"
    },
    {
      "question": "no longer frozen",
      "answer": "thawed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a female relative  ",
      "answer": "kinswoman"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a naive manner",
      "answer": "naively"
    },
    {
      "question": " unlikely to bring about favorable results or enjoyment",
      "answer": "unpromising"
    },
    {
      "question": "unclearness by virtue of having more than one meaning  ",
      "answer": "ambiguity"
    },
    {
      "question": "designed for or adapted to a function or use",
      "answer": "functional"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of applying paving materials to an area  ",
      "answer": "paving"
    },
    {
      "question": "likely to spread and cause an epidemic disease",
      "answer": "pestilent"
    },
    {
      "question": "herd and care for",
      "answer": "wrangle"
    },
    {
      "question": "make or form into a solid or hardened mass",
      "answer": "consolidate"
    },
    {
      "question": "evasively worded in order to avoid an unqualified statement  ",
      "answer": "hedged"
    },
    {
      "question": "walk slovenly  ",
      "answer": "slouch"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an early stage of development",
      "answer": "embryonic"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality or state of lacking merit or value  ",
      "answer": "unworthiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the surface decorated with a network of fine cracks, as in crackleware",
      "answer": "crackle"
    },
    {
      "question": "be about",
      "answer": "loiter"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of glass) having a roughened coating resembling frost",
      "answer": "frosted"
    },
    {
      "question": "creating nets  ",
      "answer": "netting"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who holds slaves  ",
      "answer": "slaveholder"
    },
    {
      "question": "an event that is experienced as indicating important things to come",
      "answer": "augury"
    },
    {
      "question": "the left side of a ship or aircraft to someone who is aboard and facing the bow or nose  ",
      "answer": "larboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "shrub of central and southeastern Europe",
      "answer": "mistletoe"
    },
    {
      "question": "make one's way by force",
      "answer": "muscle"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who goes before or announces the coming of another  ",
      "answer": "precursor"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of relieving ills and changing for the better  ",
      "answer": "amelioration"
    },
    {
      "question": "with great feeling",
      "answer": "feelingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking pathways",
      "answer": "pathless"
    },
    {
      "question": "go `ding dong', like a bell  ",
      "answer": "ding"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a wide variety of skills  ",
      "answer": "versatility"
    },
    {
      "question": "suffering from gout  ",
      "answer": "gouty"
    },
    {
      "question": "color or dye with a pigment",
      "answer": "pigment"
    },
    {
      "question": "not distracted by anything unrelated to the goal  ",
      "answer": "businesslike"
    },
    {
      "question": "voluntary sexual intercourse between persons not married to each other  ",
      "answer": "fornication"
    },
    {
      "question": "well articulated or enunciated, and loud enough to be heard distinctly",
      "answer": "intelligible"
    },
    {
      "question": "duplicator that transmits the copy by wire or radio  ",
      "answer": "facsimile"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a methodical manner",
      "answer": "methodically"
    },
    {
      "question": "breathe noisily during one's sleep",
      "answer": "snore"
    },
    {
      "question": "anglewing butterfly with a comma-shaped mark on the underside of each hind wing  ",
      "answer": "comma"
    },
    {
      "question": "a list of writings with time and place of publication (such as the writings of a single author or the works referred to in preparing a document etc.)  ",
      "answer": "bibliography"
    },
    {
      "question": "a closely woven silk or synthetic fabric with a narrow crosswise rib  ",
      "answer": "broadcloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "the resemblance of an animal species to another species or to natural objects",
      "answer": "mimicry"
    },
    {
      "question": "careful in regard to your own interests",
      "answer": "provident"
    },
    {
      "question": "a certificate whose value is recognized by the payer and payee",
      "answer": "scrip"
    },
    {
      "question": "entering a building unlawfully with intent to commit a felony or to steal valuable property  ",
      "answer": "burglary"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of convoking  ",
      "answer": "convocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "pronounce with a nasal twang  ",
      "answer": "twang"
    },
    {
      "question": "not capable of being distinguished or differentiated",
      "answer": "indistinguishable"
    },
    {
      "question": "the likeness of a representation to the thing represented",
      "answer": "naturalness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a religious society of women who live together as sisters (especially an order of nuns)  ",
      "answer": "sisterhood"
    },
    {
      "question": "hunt or shoot snipe  ",
      "answer": "snipe"
    },
    {
      "question": "forbidden to profane use especially in South Pacific islands  ",
      "answer": "taboo"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing patient and unruffled self-control and restraint under adversity",
      "answer": "forbearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "disturbed psychologically as if by a physical jolt or shock",
      "answer": "jolted"
    },
    {
      "question": "not experiencing or inspiring joy",
      "answer": "joyless"
    },
    {
      "question": "precise detailed study of the surface features of a region  ",
      "answer": "topography"
    },
    {
      "question": "shower with love",
      "answer": "dote"
    },
    {
      "question": "a group of persons who are engaged in a common activity",
      "answer": "platoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "small seed of any of various annual cereal grasses especially Setaria italica  ",
      "answer": "millet"
    },
    {
      "question": "in accommodation",
      "answer": "obligingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "like a sponge in being able to absorb liquids and yield it back when compressed  ",
      "answer": "spongy"
    },
    {
      "question": "to quarrel noisily, angrily or disruptively",
      "answer": "brawl"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone guided more by ideals than by practical considerations  ",
      "answer": "idealist"
    },
    {
      "question": "the first canonical hour",
      "answer": "matins"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a professional manner",
      "answer": "professionally"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing to become steady",
      "answer": "steadying"
    },
    {
      "question": "thick-branched wide-spreading tree of Africa and adjacent southwestern Asia often buttressed with branches rising from near the ground",
      "answer": "sycamore"
    },
    {
      "question": "a violent rotating windstorm  ",
      "answer": "cyclone"
    },
    {
      "question": "restraint consisting of a rope (or light chain) used to restrain an animal  ",
      "answer": "leash"
    },
    {
      "question": "warm by rubbing, as with the hands  ",
      "answer": "chafe"
    },
    {
      "question": "afflicted with or associated with pulmonary tuberculosis",
      "answer": "consumptive"
    },
    {
      "question": "produce dimples while smiling",
      "answer": "dimple"
    },
    {
      "question": "short-tailed wildcats with usually tufted ears",
      "answer": "lynx"
    },
    {
      "question": "impressiveness in scale or proportion  ",
      "answer": "stateliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "eject the contents of the stomach through the mouth",
      "answer": "vomit"
    },
    {
      "question": "twist together or entwine into a confusing mass",
      "answer": "entangle"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person is not easily classified and not very interesting  ",
      "answer": "nondescript"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of the voice) quivering as from weakness or fear",
      "answer": "quavering"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of securing possession of the rebounding basketball after a missed shot  ",
      "answer": "rebound"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who captures and holds people or animals  ",
      "answer": "captor"
    },
    {
      "question": "cast, hurl, or throw repeatedly with some missile",
      "answer": "pelt"
    },
    {
      "question": "fit to be seen",
      "answer": "presentable"
    },
    {
      "question": "concerned with or related to the past",
      "answer": "retrospective"
    },
    {
      "question": "the process of becoming stiff or rigid  ",
      "answer": "stiffening"
    },
    {
      "question": "a filmmaker who has a personal style and keeps creative control over his or her works  ",
      "answer": "auteur"
    },
    {
      "question": "affect with palsy  ",
      "answer": "palsy"
    },
    {
      "question": "not alert to danger or deception",
      "answer": "unwary"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used as a sentence connector) therefore or consequently  ",
      "answer": "ergo"
    },
    {
      "question": "a reminder of past events  ",
      "answer": "memento"
    },
    {
      "question": "the aperture of a wind instrument into which the player blows directly  ",
      "answer": "mouthpiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "being sharply insistent on being heard",
      "answer": "strident"
    },
    {
      "question": "one who trains other persons or animals  ",
      "answer": "trainer"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman author  ",
      "answer": "authoress"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to a person who is subordinate to another  ",
      "answer": "adjunct"
    },
    {
      "question": "a structure composed of a series of arches supported by columns  ",
      "answer": "arcade"
    },
    {
      "question": "grey or white wading bird with long neck and long legs and (usually) long bill  ",
      "answer": "heron"
    },
    {
      "question": "a noisy riotous fight  ",
      "answer": "melee"
    },
    {
      "question": "verging on the indecent",
      "answer": "indelicate"
    },
    {
      "question": "without possibility of separation",
      "answer": "inseparably"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman prophet  ",
      "answer": "prophetess"
    },
    {
      "question": "a covering spread over a dining table  ",
      "answer": "tablecloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "lengthen and slow down or draw out",
      "answer": "drawl"
    },
    {
      "question": "overcome by a feeling of awe  ",
      "answer": "overawed"
    },
    {
      "question": "formerly a term of respect for important white Europeans in colonial India",
      "answer": "sahib"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an impressively beautiful manner",
      "answer": "gorgeously"
    },
    {
      "question": "piety by virtue of being a godly person  ",
      "answer": "godliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a wild gathering involving excessive drinking and promiscuity  ",
      "answer": "orgy"
    },
    {
      "question": "march in a procession",
      "answer": "parade"
    },
    {
      "question": "a variety show with songs and comic acts etc.  ",
      "answer": "vaudeville"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of ordaining",
      "answer": "ordination"
    },
    {
      "question": "for a limitless time",
      "answer": "everlastingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "attracting and holding interest as if by a spell",
      "answer": "hypnotic"
    },
    {
      "question": "(physics) the smallest discrete quantity of some physical property that a system can possess (according to quantum theory)  ",
      "answer": "quantum"
    },
    {
      "question": "an impure form of quartz consisting of banded chalcedony",
      "answer": "agate"
    },
    {
      "question": "armor plate that protects the chest",
      "answer": "breastplate"
    },
    {
      "question": "burn slightly and superficially so as to affect color",
      "answer": "char"
    },
    {
      "question": "given out in portions  ",
      "answer": "apportioned"
    },
    {
      "question": "influenced or controlled by a powerful force such as a strong emotion",
      "answer": "obsessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "respiratory disease characterized by inflammation of the lung parenchyma (excluding the bronchi) with congestion caused by viruses or bacteria or irritants  ",
      "answer": "pneumonia"
    },
    {
      "question": "produce pods, of plants  ",
      "answer": "pod"
    },
    {
      "question": "an often persistent bodily disorder or disease",
      "answer": "ailment"
    },
    {
      "question": "harshness of manner  ",
      "answer": "asperity"
    },
    {
      "question": "drop (stuff) in a heap or mass",
      "answer": "dump"
    },
    {
      "question": "tilling the land with a plow",
      "answer": "plowing"
    },
    {
      "question": "large dark brown North American arboreal carnivorous mammal  ",
      "answer": "fisher"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality or character of life in a city or town",
      "answer": "urbanity"
    },
    {
      "question": "offensively malodorous",
      "answer": "fetid"
    },
    {
      "question": "(theology) the origination of the Holy Spirit at Pentecost",
      "answer": "emanation"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who reads manuscripts and judges their suitability for publication  ",
      "answer": "reviewer"
    },
    {
      "question": "cut short in duration",
      "answer": "abbreviated"
    },
    {
      "question": "promise of reward as in \"carrot and stick\"",
      "answer": "carrot"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who claims to discover hidden knowledge with the aid of supernatural powers  ",
      "answer": "diviner"
    },
    {
      "question": "not punished",
      "answer": "unpunished"
    },
    {
      "question": "a one-piece cloak worn by men in ancient Rome  ",
      "answer": "toga"
    },
    {
      "question": "not cautious or reticent",
      "answer": "unreserved"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of being blunt and outspoken  ",
      "answer": "frankness"
    },
    {
      "question": "not having a head or formed without a head ",
      "answer": "headless"
    },
    {
      "question": "perform an interlude",
      "answer": "interlude"
    },
    {
      "question": "make laws, bills, etc. or bring into effect by legislation",
      "answer": "legislate"
    },
    {
      "question": "social or solitary hymenopterans typically having a slender body with the abdomen attached by a narrow stalk and having a formidable sting  ",
      "answer": "wasp"
    },
    {
      "question": "mixture of ground animal feeds  ",
      "answer": "mash"
    },
    {
      "question": "cancel officially",
      "answer": "revoke"
    },
    {
      "question": "a holder or proprietor of land  ",
      "answer": "landowner"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman who is a patron or the wife of a patron  ",
      "answer": "patroness"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking ardor or vigor or energy",
      "answer": "spiritless"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or constituting testimony  ",
      "answer": "testimonial"
    },
    {
      "question": "large coarse fern often several feet high",
      "answer": "bracken"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing sorrow  ",
      "answer": "dolorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "to render motionless, as with a fixed stare or by arousing terror or awe",
      "answer": "fascinate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the handle of a weapon or tool  ",
      "answer": "haft"
    },
    {
      "question": "a simple machine consisting of a wheel with a groove in which a rope can run to change the direction or point of application of a force applied to the rope  ",
      "answer": "pulley"
    },
    {
      "question": "without success",
      "answer": "unsuccessfully"
    },
    {
      "question": "grant a leave to",
      "answer": "furlough"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of making something completely wet",
      "answer": "drenching"
    },
    {
      "question": "pressure or urge someone into an action  ",
      "answer": "hustle"
    },
    {
      "question": "female of any member of the dog family  ",
      "answer": "bitch"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of being comprehended or understood",
      "answer": "comprehensible"
    },
    {
      "question": "work excessively hard",
      "answer": "overwork"
    },
    {
      "question": "an effigy in the shape of a man to frighten birds away from seeds  ",
      "answer": "scarecrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "the sixth of the seven canonical hours of the divine office",
      "answer": "vespers"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pseudoscientific forerunner of chemistry in medieval times  ",
      "answer": "alchemy"
    },
    {
      "question": "send to an address  ",
      "answer": "consign"
    },
    {
      "question": "the arch of hair above each eye  ",
      "answer": "eyebrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "a storehouse for threshed grain or animal feed  ",
      "answer": "granary"
    },
    {
      "question": "suffering from or suggesting a liver disorder or gastric distress  ",
      "answer": "bilious"
    },
    {
      "question": "the social system that developed in Europe in the 8th century",
      "answer": "feudalism"
    },
    {
      "question": "the business of providing services to tourists",
      "answer": "tourism"
    },
    {
      "question": "the highest part of the back at the base of the neck of various animals especially draft animals  ",
      "answer": "withers"
    },
    {
      "question": "an annual publication containing tabular information in a particular field or fields arranged according to the calendar of a given year  ",
      "answer": "almanac"
    },
    {
      "question": "an atmospheric phenomenon consisting of bands of light caused by charged solar particles following the earth's magnetic lines of force  ",
      "answer": "aurora"
    },
    {
      "question": "providing personal satisfaction",
      "answer": "rewarding"
    },
    {
      "question": "a female confidant  ",
      "answer": "confidante"
    },
    {
      "question": "consisting of two or more associated entities",
      "answer": "conjoined"
    },
    {
      "question": "be similar in sound, especially with respect to the last syllable",
      "answer": "rhyme"
    },
    {
      "question": "loaded with something that hinders motion",
      "answer": "clogged"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to increase knowledge or dissipate ignorance",
      "answer": "enlightening"
    },
    {
      "question": "free from deception or illusion  ",
      "answer": "undeceive"
    },
    {
      "question": "hardwood from any of various locust trees  ",
      "answer": "locust"
    },
    {
      "question": "an old breed of powerful deep-chested smooth-coated dog used chiefly as a watchdog and guard dog  ",
      "answer": "mastiff"
    },
    {
      "question": "the commonest type of solidified lava",
      "answer": "basalt"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a picturesque manner",
      "answer": "picturesquely"
    },
    {
      "question": "cut into cubes",
      "answer": "cube"
    },
    {
      "question": "person who does no work",
      "answer": "idler"
    },
    {
      "question": "equip (a horse) with a horseshoe or horseshoes  ",
      "answer": "horseshoe"
    },
    {
      "question": "a permanent diplomatic mission headed by a minister  ",
      "answer": "legation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the feeling of being bored by something tedious  ",
      "answer": "boredom"
    },
    {
      "question": "the mathematical process of obtaining the derivative of a function  ",
      "answer": "differentiation"
    },
    {
      "question": "impossible of undergoing division",
      "answer": "indivisible"
    },
    {
      "question": "a field on which the buildings of a university are situated  ",
      "answer": "campus"
    },
    {
      "question": "the science concerned with the prevention of illness and maintenance of health  ",
      "answer": "hygiene"
    },
    {
      "question": "a company that moves the possessions of a family or business from one site to another  ",
      "answer": "mover"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mayor or chief magistrate of a Spanish town  ",
      "answer": "alcalde"
    },
    {
      "question": "urge or force (a person) to an action",
      "answer": "impel"
    },
    {
      "question": "unskillfulness resulting from a lack of efficiency  ",
      "answer": "inefficiency"
    },
    {
      "question": "a fastener that locks or closes  ",
      "answer": "locker"
    },
    {
      "question": "confidentially or in secret",
      "answer": "privily"
    },
    {
      "question": "a communal dining-hall (usually in a monastery)  ",
      "answer": "refectory"
    },
    {
      "question": "meet to select a candidate or promote a policy  ",
      "answer": "caucus"
    },
    {
      "question": "take the load off (a container or vehicle)",
      "answer": "unload"
    },
    {
      "question": "given to or characterized by argument",
      "answer": "argumentative"
    },
    {
      "question": "a stringed instrument of the guitar family that has long neck and circular body  ",
      "answer": "banjo"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or provided with a belt",
      "answer": "belted"
    },
    {
      "question": "destroy by firepower, such as an enemy's line of communication  ",
      "answer": "interdict"
    },
    {
      "question": "color a moderate to strong red  ",
      "answer": "madder"
    },
    {
      "question": "commodities offered for sale",
      "answer": "merchandise"
    },
    {
      "question": "a schemer who tries to gain advantage in an organization in sly or underhanded ways  ",
      "answer": "politician"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who rides the near horse of a pair in order to guide the horses pulling a carriage (especially a carriage without a coachman)  ",
      "answer": "postilion"
    },
    {
      "question": "freed of dependence on something especially (for mammals) mother's milk",
      "answer": "weaned"
    },
    {
      "question": "a double sulphate of aluminum and potassium that is used as an astringent (among other things)  ",
      "answer": "alum"
    },
    {
      "question": "quality of coming late or later in time  ",
      "answer": "lateness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a hard brittle grey polyvalent metallic element that resembles iron but is not magnetic",
      "answer": "manganese"
    },
    {
      "question": "cook or heat in a microwave oven",
      "answer": "microwave"
    },
    {
      "question": "personal independence  ",
      "answer": "autonomy"
    },
    {
      "question": "hold within limits and control",
      "answer": "mortify"
    },
    {
      "question": "designed or suitable for competing in a race  ",
      "answer": "racy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sharp sound made by small birds or insects  ",
      "answer": "chirp"
    },
    {
      "question": "transfer by a lease or by a will  ",
      "answer": "demise"
    },
    {
      "question": "excessive or insincere praise  ",
      "answer": "flattery"
    },
    {
      "question": "a document certifying the successful completion of a course of study  ",
      "answer": "diploma"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an authoritative and magisterial manner",
      "answer": "authoritatively"
    },
    {
      "question": "an organism of the kingdom Fungi lacking chlorophyll and feeding on organic matter",
      "answer": "fungus"
    },
    {
      "question": "not returned in kind",
      "answer": "unanswered"
    },
    {
      "question": "beliefs of a person or social group in which they have an emotional investment (either for or against something)",
      "answer": "values"
    },
    {
      "question": "ascent by or as if by a ladder  ",
      "answer": "scaling"
    },
    {
      "question": "a conduit that resembles a bridge but carries water over a valley  ",
      "answer": "aqueduct"
    },
    {
      "question": "a careless leisurely gait",
      "answer": "saunter"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman's close-fitting hat that resembles a helmet  ",
      "answer": "cloche"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an identifiably distinctive manner",
      "answer": "distinctively"
    },
    {
      "question": "accompanied by bloodshed",
      "answer": "gory"
    },
    {
      "question": "disturb (someone's) composure",
      "answer": "jolt"
    },
    {
      "question": "an act of being a tenant or occupant  ",
      "answer": "occupancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "especially a light saddle horse for a woman  ",
      "answer": "palfrey"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sudden sharp increase in the relative numbers of a population  ",
      "answer": "irruption"
    },
    {
      "question": "extreme care in spending money",
      "answer": "parsimony"
    },
    {
      "question": "an employee of a bank who receives and pays out money  ",
      "answer": "teller"
    },
    {
      "question": "a useful or valuable quality  ",
      "answer": "asset"
    },
    {
      "question": "more readily or willingly",
      "answer": "preferably"
    },
    {
      "question": "(music) calibrating something (an instrument or electronic circuit) to a standard frequency  ",
      "answer": "tuning"
    },
    {
      "question": "dedicated in fulfillment of a vow",
      "answer": "votive"
    },
    {
      "question": "enclose or enfold completely with or as if with a covering",
      "answer": "envelop"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or produced by or consisting of molecules",
      "answer": "molecular"
    },
    {
      "question": "(especially of rows as of troops or mountains) pressed together",
      "answer": "serried"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking necessary force for effectiveness",
      "answer": "toothless"
    },
    {
      "question": "a flock of birds (especially when gathered close together on the ground)",
      "answer": "bevy"
    },
    {
      "question": "live on or in a host, as of parasites  ",
      "answer": "infest"
    },
    {
      "question": "(physics) a dynamical system that is extremely sensitive to its initial conditions  ",
      "answer": "chaos"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a dangerous manner",
      "answer": "perilously"
    },
    {
      "question": "the criminal class  ",
      "answer": "underworld"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being new",
      "answer": "newness"
    },
    {
      "question": "of plants or persons",
      "answer": "parasitic"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide or cover with a cloak  ",
      "answer": "vesture"
    },
    {
      "question": "(computer science) a program that decodes instructions written in a higher order language and produces an assembly language program  ",
      "answer": "compiler"
    },
    {
      "question": "excessive crowding",
      "answer": "congestion"
    },
    {
      "question": "write, draw, or trace with a crayon  ",
      "answer": "crayon"
    },
    {
      "question": "enter a demurrer  ",
      "answer": "demur"
    },
    {
      "question": "give the keynote address to (an audience)  ",
      "answer": "keynote"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being plausible or acceptable to a reasonable person",
      "answer": "reasonableness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the object of cursing or detestation",
      "answer": "execration"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small high-pitched flute similar to a piccolo",
      "answer": "fife"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or distinguished by a tone",
      "answer": "toned"
    },
    {
      "question": "suitable for or like a palace",
      "answer": "palatial"
    },
    {
      "question": "work lightly",
      "answer": "potter"
    },
    {
      "question": "stain (skin) with indelible color  ",
      "answer": "tattoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of running away with a lover (usually to get married)  ",
      "answer": "elopement"
    },
    {
      "question": "give equal rights to",
      "answer": "emancipate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being improbable",
      "answer": "improbability"
    },
    {
      "question": "a religious ceremony in which something is made holy  ",
      "answer": "sanctification"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause a stinging or tingling sensation  ",
      "answer": "tingle"
    },
    {
      "question": "affected with paralysis  ",
      "answer": "paralytic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a seal (especially one used to mark documents officially)  ",
      "answer": "signet"
    },
    {
      "question": "upward on a hill or incline",
      "answer": "uphill"
    },
    {
      "question": "of an appropriate or pertinent nature  ",
      "answer": "apropos"
    },
    {
      "question": "a political leader who seeks support by appealing to popular passions and prejudices  ",
      "answer": "demagogue"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or existing at or near the geographic equator",
      "answer": "equatorial"
    },
    {
      "question": "with honey added  ",
      "answer": "honeyed"
    },
    {
      "question": "treat or speak of with contempt",
      "answer": "deride"
    },
    {
      "question": "used of a person in the first year of an experience (especially in United States high school or college)",
      "answer": "freshman"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an uncalled-for manner",
      "answer": "gratuitously"
    },
    {
      "question": "begin again",
      "answer": "recommence"
    },
    {
      "question": "driven by lust",
      "answer": "lascivious"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a providential manner",
      "answer": "providentially"
    },
    {
      "question": "reclaimed by payment of a ransom  ",
      "answer": "ransomed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a holding device attached to a workbench",
      "answer": "vise"
    },
    {
      "question": "summon with a wave, nod, or some other gesture  ",
      "answer": "beckon"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of forsaking  ",
      "answer": "forsaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "of animals or fruits that have a shell  ",
      "answer": "shelled"
    },
    {
      "question": "(music) the distinctive property of a complex sound (a voice or noise or musical sound)",
      "answer": "timbre"
    },
    {
      "question": "a three-legged rack used for support  ",
      "answer": "tripod"
    },
    {
      "question": "with desperation",
      "answer": "despairingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "maneuver into a dock",
      "answer": "dock"
    },
    {
      "question": "an early limited awareness of something yet to occur  ",
      "answer": "foretaste"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of not being suitable",
      "answer": "unfitness"
    },
    {
      "question": "attack with fusillade  ",
      "answer": "fusillade"
    },
    {
      "question": "proper respect",
      "answer": "props"
    },
    {
      "question": "seemingly loud enough to break something",
      "answer": "shattering"
    },
    {
      "question": "a stream or brook  ",
      "answer": "arroyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "a reward or payment  ",
      "answer": "guerdon"
    },
    {
      "question": "a yearning for something or to do something  ",
      "answer": "hankering"
    },
    {
      "question": "a clear liquid secreted into the mouth by the salivary glands and mucous glands of the mouth",
      "answer": "saliva"
    },
    {
      "question": "gradual improvement or growth or development",
      "answer": "advancement"
    },
    {
      "question": "two-masted sailing vessel square-rigged on the foremast and fore-and-aft rigged on the mainmast  ",
      "answer": "brigantine"
    },
    {
      "question": "the work of cleaning and running a house  ",
      "answer": "housework"
    },
    {
      "question": "destructive of morale and self-reliance  ",
      "answer": "demoralizing"
    },
    {
      "question": "successive change from one thing or state to another and back again",
      "answer": "alternation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the exposure of falseness or pretensions",
      "answer": "repudiation"
    },
    {
      "question": "hunt with ferrets  ",
      "answer": "ferret"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who respects someone or something",
      "answer": "respecter"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing thoughtlessness",
      "answer": "thoughtlessly"
    },
    {
      "question": "(physiology) the automatic adjustment in focal length of the natural lens of the eye  ",
      "answer": "accommodation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the person in charge of the bank in a gambling game  ",
      "answer": "banker"
    },
    {
      "question": "within doors",
      "answer": "indoor"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of moving freely  ",
      "answer": "mobility"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a negligent manner",
      "answer": "negligently"
    },
    {
      "question": "not genuine or natural",
      "answer": "synthetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "not under constraint in action or expression",
      "answer": "unbuttoned"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the process of hearing",
      "answer": "auditory"
    },
    {
      "question": "involving or constituting a cause",
      "answer": "causal"
    },
    {
      "question": "represented accurately or precisely  ",
      "answer": "delineated"
    },
    {
      "question": "skill in handling and riding horses  ",
      "answer": "horsemanship"
    },
    {
      "question": "make or become black",
      "answer": "blacken"
    },
    {
      "question": "travel by tram  ",
      "answer": "tram"
    },
    {
      "question": "written declaration made under oath",
      "answer": "affidavit"
    },
    {
      "question": "a compensating equivalent  ",
      "answer": "counterbalance"
    },
    {
      "question": "lose in value",
      "answer": "depreciate"
    },
    {
      "question": "connect with a tee",
      "answer": "tee"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being subject to variation  ",
      "answer": "variability"
    },
    {
      "question": "any object that can be used to hold things (especially a large metal boxlike object of standardized dimensions that can be loaded from one form of transport to another)  ",
      "answer": "container"
    },
    {
      "question": "the mistake of misrepresenting the facts  ",
      "answer": "distortion"
    },
    {
      "question": "shout out",
      "answer": "holler"
    },
    {
      "question": "with all your strength",
      "answer": "amain"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by plundering or pillaging or marauding",
      "answer": "marauding"
    },
    {
      "question": "creating a favorable impression",
      "answer": "prepossessing"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small shallow-draft boat carrying mounted guns",
      "answer": "gunboat"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of defending or explaining or making excuses for by reasoning",
      "answer": "justification"
    },
    {
      "question": "based on or arising from the possession of money or wealth",
      "answer": "moneyed"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by great swelling waves or surges",
      "answer": "billowy"
    },
    {
      "question": "affect in a contagious way",
      "answer": "infect"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a long sharp point  ",
      "answer": "spiked"
    },
    {
      "question": "inspiring a feeling of fear",
      "answer": "eerie"
    },
    {
      "question": "blowing in puffs or short intermittent blasts",
      "answer": "gusty"
    },
    {
      "question": "where the air is unconfined",
      "answer": "outdoors"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of verse) having a metric system based on relative duration of syllables",
      "answer": "quantitative"
    },
    {
      "question": "fleshy hindquarters",
      "answer": "rump"
    },
    {
      "question": "to compress with violence, out of natural shape or condition",
      "answer": "squash"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sum of money allotted on a regular basis",
      "answer": "stipend"
    },
    {
      "question": "large somewhat primitive fish-eating diving bird of the northern hemisphere having webbed feet placed far back",
      "answer": "loon"
    },
    {
      "question": "shape or form to required dimensions  ",
      "answer": "dimension"
    },
    {
      "question": "a gradual decline of something",
      "answer": "erosion"
    },
    {
      "question": "an injury that causes disfigurement or that deprives you of a limb or other important body part  ",
      "answer": "mutilation"
    },
    {
      "question": "approve officially",
      "answer": "visa"
    },
    {
      "question": "not faithful to religion or party or cause  ",
      "answer": "apostate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a forest fire fighter who is sent to battle remote and severe forest fires (often for days at a time)  ",
      "answer": "coyote"
    },
    {
      "question": "exhale spasmodically, as when an irritant entered one's nose",
      "answer": "sneeze"
    },
    {
      "question": "steadfast resolution  ",
      "answer": "steadfastness"
    },
    {
      "question": "untouched or undefiled",
      "answer": "virginal"
    },
    {
      "question": "an opaque form of quartz",
      "answer": "jasper"
    },
    {
      "question": "any triangular fore-and-aft sail (set forward of the foremast)  ",
      "answer": "jib"
    },
    {
      "question": "inducing mental lethargy",
      "answer": "narcotic"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or joined by a seam or seams  ",
      "answer": "seamed"
    },
    {
      "question": "exciting by touching lightly so as to cause laughter or twitching movements  ",
      "answer": "tickling"
    },
    {
      "question": "the enchanted realm of fairies  ",
      "answer": "fairyland"
    },
    {
      "question": "support by being a patron of  ",
      "answer": "patronage"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bill for an amount due  ",
      "answer": "reckoning"
    },
    {
      "question": "the activity of superscribing  ",
      "answer": "superscription"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a useless manner",
      "answer": "uselessly"
    },
    {
      "question": "persuade through constant efforts  ",
      "answer": "badger"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause blisters to form on",
      "answer": "blister"
    },
    {
      "question": "the anxiety you experience when you feel vulnerable and insecure  ",
      "answer": "insecurity"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who plays the bagpipe  ",
      "answer": "piper"
    },
    {
      "question": "hold (someone's attention)",
      "answer": "rivet"
    },
    {
      "question": "of many different kinds purposefully arranged but lacking any uniformity",
      "answer": "assorted"
    },
    {
      "question": "theater light at the front of a stage that illuminate the set and actors  ",
      "answer": "footlights"
    },
    {
      "question": "a ribald person",
      "answer": "ribald"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who deals tactfully with others  ",
      "answer": "diplomat"
    },
    {
      "question": "an angel ranked above the highest rank in the celestial hierarchy  ",
      "answer": "archangel"
    },
    {
      "question": "degradation of something worthy of respect",
      "answer": "profanation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman shepherd  ",
      "answer": "shepherdess"
    },
    {
      "question": "a loose-fitting white ecclesiastical vestment with wide sleeves  ",
      "answer": "surplice"
    },
    {
      "question": "a game similar to field hockey but played on horseback using long-handled mallets and a wooden ball  ",
      "answer": "polo"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover with or as with a cowl",
      "answer": "cowl"
    },
    {
      "question": "front illustration facing the title page of a book  ",
      "answer": "frontispiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "state of disgrace resulting from public abuse  ",
      "answer": "obloquy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of giving special importance or significance to something  ",
      "answer": "emphasizing"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who works only for money  ",
      "answer": "hireling"
    },
    {
      "question": "the vestments and other insignia of a pontiff (especially a bishop)  ",
      "answer": "pontifical"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling steel in hardness  ",
      "answer": "steely"
    },
    {
      "question": "adhering to established customs or doctrines (especially in religion)  ",
      "answer": "conforming"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who hates  ",
      "answer": "hater"
    },
    {
      "question": "formally reject or disavow a formerly held belief, usually under pressure",
      "answer": "abjure"
    },
    {
      "question": "the sport of shooting arrows with a bow  ",
      "answer": "archery"
    },
    {
      "question": "with the least delay",
      "answer": "soonest"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ordinal number of one thousand in counting order  ",
      "answer": "thousandth"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an unfair manner",
      "answer": "unfairly"
    },
    {
      "question": "rendered unwholesome by contaminants and pollution",
      "answer": "contaminated"
    },
    {
      "question": "a thin wire (usually tungsten) that is heated white hot by the passage of an electric current  ",
      "answer": "filament"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a grotesque manner",
      "answer": "grotesquely"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various fishes of the family Scombridae  ",
      "answer": "mackerel"
    },
    {
      "question": "covered with or as if with clothes or a wrap or cloak",
      "answer": "cloaked"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who leads you to believe something that is not true  ",
      "answer": "deceiver"
    },
    {
      "question": "containing or composed of fat",
      "answer": "fatty"
    },
    {
      "question": "a preschool for children age 4 to 6 to prepare them for primary school  ",
      "answer": "kindergarten"
    },
    {
      "question": "a stone pillar having a rectangular cross section tapering towards a pyramidal top  ",
      "answer": "obelisk"
    },
    {
      "question": "(15-16th century) any armor for the head",
      "answer": "casque"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a lofty manner",
      "answer": "loftily"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bitter alkaloid extracted from chinchona bark",
      "answer": "quinine"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ability to deal resourcefully with unusual problems",
      "answer": "resource"
    },
    {
      "question": "partly close one's eyes, as when hit by direct blinding light",
      "answer": "squint"
    },
    {
      "question": "a regional term for `creature' (especially for domestic animals)  ",
      "answer": "critter"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of rain) falling lightly in very small drops",
      "answer": "drizzling"
    },
    {
      "question": "using exactly the same words",
      "answer": "verbatim"
    },
    {
      "question": "the mark (') used to indicate the omission of one or more letters from a printed word  ",
      "answer": "apostrophe"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to a climate",
      "answer": "climatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "make fat or plump",
      "answer": "fatten"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pen for livestock in southern Africa  ",
      "answer": "kraal"
    },
    {
      "question": "untroubled by dreams",
      "answer": "dreamless"
    },
    {
      "question": "the process of oxidizing",
      "answer": "oxidation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a missile equipped with a device that is attracted toward some kind of emission (heat or light or sound or radio waves)  ",
      "answer": "seeker"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a tentative manner",
      "answer": "tentatively"
    },
    {
      "question": "not decorated with something to increase its beauty or distinction  ",
      "answer": "unadorned"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by no noteworthy or significant events",
      "answer": "uneventful"
    },
    {
      "question": "an optical phenomenon resulting from the failure of a lens or mirror to produce a good image  ",
      "answer": "aberration"
    },
    {
      "question": "the leg from the knee to foot  ",
      "answer": "crus"
    },
    {
      "question": "from or at a distance",
      "answer": "distantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "chop up",
      "answer": "hash"
    },
    {
      "question": "be a regular customer or client of",
      "answer": "patronize"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a relentless manner",
      "answer": "relentlessly"
    },
    {
      "question": "hit hard",
      "answer": "whack"
    },
    {
      "question": "the use of dye to change the color of something permanently  ",
      "answer": "dyeing"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or concerning this",
      "answer": "hereof"
    },
    {
      "question": "a speech of violent denunciation  ",
      "answer": "tirade"
    },
    {
      "question": "bound by contract  ",
      "answer": "apprenticed"
    },
    {
      "question": "obtain through threats  ",
      "answer": "blackmail"
    },
    {
      "question": "present at birth but not necessarily hereditary",
      "answer": "congenital"
    },
    {
      "question": "as from opposite ends of a diameter",
      "answer": "diametrically"
    },
    {
      "question": "a tool resembling a hammer but with a large head (usually wooden)",
      "answer": "mallet"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of severing  ",
      "answer": "severance"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a stolid manner",
      "answer": "stolidly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a feeling of anger caused by being offended",
      "answer": "umbrage"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an abnormal manner",
      "answer": "abnormally"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing or constituting penance",
      "answer": "penitential"
    },
    {
      "question": "a member of a fire department who tries to extinguish fires  ",
      "answer": "fireman"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a joyous and gleeful manner",
      "answer": "gleefully"
    },
    {
      "question": "with respect to its inherent nature",
      "answer": "intrinsically"
    },
    {
      "question": "an officer aboard a ship who keeps accounts and attends to the passengers' welfare  ",
      "answer": "purser"
    },
    {
      "question": "plants having long green or reddish acidic leafstalks growing in basal clumps",
      "answer": "rhubarb"
    },
    {
      "question": "restrict",
      "answer": "stiffen"
    },
    {
      "question": "a localized and violently destructive windstorm occurring over land characterized by a funnel-shaped cloud extending toward the ground  ",
      "answer": "tornado"
    },
    {
      "question": "anesthetize with chloroform",
      "answer": "chloroform"
    },
    {
      "question": "twisted (especially as in pain or struggle)",
      "answer": "contorted"
    },
    {
      "question": "with superficial plausibility",
      "answer": "glibly"
    },
    {
      "question": "moody and melancholic  ",
      "answer": "glum"
    },
    {
      "question": "usually paved outdoor area adjoining a residence  ",
      "answer": "patio"
    },
    {
      "question": "hoist up or in and lash or secure with a small rope  ",
      "answer": "trice"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the study of hydraulics",
      "answer": "hydraulic"
    },
    {
      "question": "severe disapproval  ",
      "answer": "reprobation"
    },
    {
      "question": "thorny evergreen small tree or shrub of India widely cultivated for its large lemonlike fruits that have thick warty rind  ",
      "answer": "citron"
    },
    {
      "question": "an act of mass destruction and loss of life (especially in war or by fire)",
      "answer": "holocaust"
    },
    {
      "question": "coniferous shrub or small tree with berrylike cones  ",
      "answer": "juniper"
    },
    {
      "question": "the yarn woven across the warp yarn in weaving  ",
      "answer": "woof"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a face indicating disgust or dislike",
      "answer": "wince"
    },
    {
      "question": "exciting sexual desire",
      "answer": "provocative"
    },
    {
      "question": "assign a time slot",
      "answer": "slot"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a bad disposition",
      "answer": "churlish"
    },
    {
      "question": "with delight",
      "answer": "delightedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a yearning manner",
      "answer": "longingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a noisy fight  ",
      "answer": "affray"
    },
    {
      "question": "young of various large placental mammals e.g. whale or giraffe or elephant or buffalo  ",
      "answer": "calf"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of subjecting someone to unwanted or improper sexual advances or activity (especially women or children)  ",
      "answer": "molestation"
    },
    {
      "question": "remaining the same for indefinitely long times  ",
      "answer": "changeless"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who devises plots or intrigues",
      "answer": "designer"
    },
    {
      "question": "a form of government in which the ruler is an absolute dictator (not restricted by a constitution or laws or opposition etc.)  ",
      "answer": "dictatorship"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a drowsy manner",
      "answer": "drowsily"
    },
    {
      "question": "used informally",
      "answer": "leaky"
    },
    {
      "question": "a power of attorney document given by shareholders of a corporation authorizing a specific vote on their behalf at a corporate meeting  ",
      "answer": "proxy"
    },
    {
      "question": "wearing a wedding ring",
      "answer": "ringed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a loud harsh or strident noise  ",
      "answer": "blare"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by speed and efficiency  ",
      "answer": "expeditious"
    },
    {
      "question": "red or black edible aggregate berries usually smaller than the related blackberries  ",
      "answer": "raspberry"
    },
    {
      "question": "not offending",
      "answer": "unoffending"
    },
    {
      "question": "a feeling of calm",
      "answer": "calmness"
    },
    {
      "question": "composed of heterogeneous elements gathered into a mass",
      "answer": "conglomerate"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or adjacent to the forehead or frontal bone",
      "answer": "frontal"
    },
    {
      "question": "immune to attack",
      "answer": "invulnerable"
    },
    {
      "question": "inconsequential conversation",
      "answer": "nothings"
    },
    {
      "question": "throw violently",
      "answer": "slam"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or containing an alkali",
      "answer": "alkaline"
    },
    {
      "question": "a purgative made from the leaves of aloe  ",
      "answer": "aloes"
    },
    {
      "question": "appealing to or stimulating the appetite especially in appearance or aroma  ",
      "answer": "appetizing"
    },
    {
      "question": "a strong declaration of protest  ",
      "answer": "protestation"
    },
    {
      "question": "spread throughout",
      "answer": "riddled"
    },
    {
      "question": "(pharmacology) the extraction of water-soluble drug substances by boiling  ",
      "answer": "decoction"
    },
    {
      "question": "an advocate of democratic principles  ",
      "answer": "democrat"
    },
    {
      "question": "guided by whim and fancy",
      "answer": "flighty"
    },
    {
      "question": "suitable for cutting or piercing",
      "answer": "incisive"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or employing dialectic",
      "answer": "dialectic"
    },
    {
      "question": "an intelligent dog with a heavy curly solid-colored coat that is usually clipped",
      "answer": "poodle"
    },
    {
      "question": "thick woolen fabric used for clothing",
      "answer": "tweed"
    },
    {
      "question": "reserved in advance  ",
      "answer": "booked"
    },
    {
      "question": "a shield",
      "answer": "escutcheon"
    },
    {
      "question": "a formal written offer to sell securities (filed with the SEC) that sets forth a plan for a (proposed) business enterprise",
      "answer": "prospectus"
    },
    {
      "question": "pit viper with horny segments at the end of the tail that rattle when shaken  ",
      "answer": "rattlesnake"
    },
    {
      "question": "feeling or expressing regret or sorrow or a sense of loss over something done or undone",
      "answer": "regretful"
    },
    {
      "question": "containing salt",
      "answer": "saline"
    },
    {
      "question": "the office and authority of a general  ",
      "answer": "generalship"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of several shrubs and vines of the genus Jasminum chiefly native to Asia  ",
      "answer": "jasmine"
    },
    {
      "question": "express a negative opinion of",
      "answer": "disparage"
    },
    {
      "question": "one praying humbly for something",
      "answer": "petitioner"
    },
    {
      "question": "a disposition to find (or make) causes for amusement",
      "answer": "playfulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "personal as opposed to real property",
      "answer": "chattel"
    }
  ]
}